# Reuben Hawthorne-Jensen

Kia ora tatou,

My name is Reuben, and if you're reading this then you must have an exciting role available that I think I would be a great fit for.

The following pages contain a summary of my skills and work experience, but after a decade in the workforce there's so much that I can't fit on the page. Despite this, here's a brief summary:

I know that I get excited when there's a problem to solve. I love the process of learning something new and unpacking the complexity of a new, undeciphered puzzle.

Once I understand the principles that lurk beneath an issue, I like to take a moment to process what I've learnt. Only then can I repackage my new found knowledge to apply it to the task at hand.

I also believe that knowledge is meant to be shared. My background in communications helps me to distill a range of complex topics and share my understanding with others.

I'm ready to talk about how I can bring value to your team. Let's grab a coffee and chat about how we can work together to build something awesome.

## qualifications

## **Bachelor of Commerce in Marketing**

Victoria University of Wellington 2014–2017

## Bachelor of Arts in Media Studies and Theatre

Victoria University of Wellington 2014–2017

### **IC Agile Certified Professional**

Awarded May 2022

## Web Developer Bootcamp 2022 (Udemy)

Completed September 2022

#### Certificate in Te Reo Māori (level 3)

Te Wānanga o Raukawa Competed 2020

## community involvement

## **Executive Member**

Wellington Thai Boxing

2021 - Present

Duties include administration of the club website and social media and collaborating with the ELT on other matters relating to running the club.

### **Muay Thai Trainer**

Wellington Thai Boxing

2020 - Present

Teaching Muay Thai classes to students with a range of skill levels from beginners to fight training.

#### **Community Event Facilitator**

2021 - Present

Coordinating and running small group exercises, involving clear communication, critical thinking and creative problem solving in a fast-paced, highly collaborative environment.

## referees

Available on request

## contact



027 936 4948



reuben.jensen11@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/reubenjensen95

## Relevant Work Experience

November 2021 - Present	<ul> <li>Web &amp; Social Media Advisor   NZEI Te Riu Roa</li> <li>Project management of the development of NZEI Te Riu Roa's new, consolidated website.</li> <li>Involved merging seven different web properties into one website, in consultation with staff and members of the organisation.</li> <li>Collaborative problem solving to support organising and campaign activities with digital tools and solutions.</li> <li>Development of minor front-end features, such as responsive header layouts, template modificatins, and simple calculators (Javascript).</li> <li>Maintaining and updating content across NZEI Te Riu Roa's existing web properties.</li> </ul>
May 2020 - October 2021	<ul> <li>Marketing Executive   Storbie</li> <li>Maintaining and updating content on the old Storbie website (ASP.NET framemework, CSHTML and SASS)</li> <li>Project management of Storbie's new website build (Umbraco CMS)</li> <li>Development of front end features for the new site including the pricing page, feature grid and automated pop-up for lead capture.</li> <li>End-to-end management and implementation of Storbie's marketing strategy.</li> </ul>
Jan 2021 - Present	<ul> <li>Website Development   Freelance/Self-employeed</li> <li>Design and build websites for clients (Wordpress, Craft CMS)</li> <li>Deploy websites to cloud hosting providers.</li> <li>Manage DNS records, support with domain authentication for email and third party apps.</li> </ul>
May 2019 - June 2020	<ul> <li>Marketing Coordinator   Creative HQ</li> <li>Managing websites for Creative HQ's three main brands (CHQ, Lightning Lab and GovTech).</li> <li>Planning, implementation and training (internal and external) of digital tools to enable digital workshops during the level 4 lockdown in 2020.</li> </ul>
January 2018 - May 2019	<ul> <li>Account Executive   Isentia</li> <li>Providing technical support and guidance to maximise the value of Isentia's products.</li> <li>Working with clients to understand their needs, optimise their service.</li> <li>Strategic relationship managment with a view to grow opportunities within client accounts.</li> </ul>
August 2016 - January 2018	Daily Briefings Editor   Isentia
July 2016 - July 2017	Tutor   Victoria Business School
December 2015 - February 2017	Driver   Tranzit Coachlines
July 2015 - August 2016	Porter / Receptionist   Copthorne Hotel Oriental Bay
January 2014 - July 2015	Insurance Sales Consultant   Cigna Life Insurance
June 2012 - December 2013	Retail Assistant   Warehouse Stationery